(Bernadette:)What did he say?
"Hi, how are you?
I was wondering
(Amy:)if you'd like to get a drink
after work sometime."
(Penny:)Well, what are
you gonna do?
(Woman:)I don't know.
(Amy:)I guess I assumed that I would
eventually date other people,
(Amy:)but this is happening so fast.
(Bernadette:)What can it hurt?
(Amy:)Well, I was hoping the
next person I dated
(Amy:)would be a little
less like Sheldon.
(Bernadette:)You mean, not a scientist?
(Penny:)I think she means not a weirdo.
(Bernadette:)Are you attracted
to him?
(Woman:)I don't know.
(Penny:)All right, well, what happens
if you imagine him naked?
(Amy:)Oh, I don't have to imagine it.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)I smell funny.
(Sheldon:)I taste salty.
(Leonard:)You're just sweaty
from exercise.
(Sheldon:)And kind of delicious.
(Sheldon:)I wonder how many licks it would
take to get to the center of me.